iimb.ac.in 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Top Management School in India, World, IIM | IIM Bangalore

**Privacy Statement**  
Thank you for visiting the IIMB website operated by the Indian Institute of Management Bangalore (IIMB). Visitors to [www.iimb.ernet.in](http://www.iimb.ernet.in/) are guaranteed privacy. Information collected on [http://www.iimb.ernet.in](http://www.iimb.ernet.in/) is kept private and never shared with other organizations. We’re making this privacy statement to inform you about the types of information gathered and disseminated on the Website.

**Measuring Audiences**  
Your IP (Internet Protocol) address is used to gather broad demographic information. IIMB logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes. These logs are analyzed constantly to improve the value of the materials available on this Website. Your IP address also helps us diagnose problems with our server and administer the Website. IP addresses do not provide us with any identifiable personal information. This means your session will be tracked, but you will remain anonymous to us.

**Cookies**  
In order to better understand the way our websites are used by visitors, IIMB employs the use of cookies, a small file that stores information on your hard disk drive. IIMB uses information derived from cookies strictly for tracking usage and developing site improvements.

**Outside Links**  
This site contains links to sites outside [www.iimb.ernet.in](http://www.iimb.ernet.in/). IIMB is not responsible for the privacy practices, or the content, of such other Websites.

**Submitting Personal Information**  
You can submit information to [www.iimb.ernet.in](http://www.iimb.ernet.in/) in several places on the Website. A ‘Contact Us’ form allows customers to request information. The form requests visitors’ contact information such as their email address and/or mailing address. Contact information from the feedback form is used to send responses or information requested by our customers. This information is never shared; it is used only for our replies.

**Site Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Children’s Guidelines**  
IIMB does not knowingly collect identifiable personal information from children under age 13. A parent or guardian must initiate any requests for information from children under the age of 13 on their behalf. We encourage parents to supervise children when they browse the Internet.

**Privacy protection**  
IIMB does not utilize direct mail services or telemarketing so your information will never be used for solicitation.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please email: [info@iimb.ernet.in](mailto:info@iimb.ernet.in)
